brothers and sisters to another
Wednesday question and answer where we
open up with the ten commandments that
God commanded for the whole world to
keep. Brother James,
>> yes sir. And God spake all these words,
saying, I am the Lord thy God, which
have brought thee out of the land of
Egypt, out of the house of bondage. Thou
shalt have no other gods before me. Thou
shalt not make unto thee any graven
image, or any likeness of anything that
is in heaven above, or that is in the
earth beneath, or that is in the water
under the earth. Thou shalt not bow down
thyself to them, nor serve them. For I,
the Lord thy God, am a jealous God,
visiting the iniquity of the fathers
upon the children unto the third and
fourth generation of them that hate me,
and showing mercy unto thousands of them
that love me, and keep my commandments.
Thou shalt not take the name of the Lord
thy God in vain. For the Lord will not
hold him guiltless that taketh his name
in vain. Remember the Sabbath day to
keep it holy. Six days shalt thou labor
and do all thy work, but the seventh day
is the Sabbath of the Lord thy God. In
it thou shalt not do any work, thou nor
thy son, nor thy daughter, thy man's
servant, nor thy maid servant, nor thy
cattle, nor thy stranger that is within
thy gates. For in six days the Lord made
heaven and earth, the sea, and all that
in them is, and rested the seventh day.
Wherefore the Lord blessed the Sabbath
day, and hollowed it. Honor thy father
and thy mother, that thy days may be
long upon the land, which the Lord thy
God giveth thee. Thou shalt not kill.
Thou shalt not commit adultery. Thou
shalt not steal. Thou shalt not bear
false witness against thy neighbor. Thou
shalt not coveret thy neighbor's house.
Thou shalt not covet thy neighbor's
wife, nor as man's servant, nor as maid
servant, nor as ox, nor assh, nor
anything that is thy neighbors. I read
Exodus 20:es 1-17. May the Lord add a
blessing to the reading of this word. In
Jesus name we pray. Amen.
>> Amen. Amen. So here on question and
answer, you can ask us a question and
we'll answer it according to the King
James Bible. And if we cannot find the
answer, we will seek further counsel to
bring you an answer at a later time. The
questions we will not answer are the
vague as well as the long scripture
questions and questions of debate. We
are not here to debate. We are here to
spread the true gospel of Jesus. So
please be as direct as possible with
your questions so we can be as direct as
possible with our answers out of the
King James Bible. No other Bibles or
books will be acknowledged on this
program. Also, keep in mind that this is
a live stream, so feel free to send in
your questions that pertain to
everlasting life. We just ask that you
please keep those questions to a two
scripture maximum. Let me introduce you
to the family that's on the panel this
evening. Brother Jerome,
>> grace and peace.
>> Brother Dre,
>> good evening. Brother Julius,
>> good evening everybody.
>> Brother James,
>> good evening everyone.
>> Sister Deborah,
>> good evening.
>> Brother Sean,
>> And we have the guest caller with us and
I'm brother Cornell. What is our first
question of the evening?
>> Uh, yes, brother Cornell. There are
several held over questions that will be
answered first before getting into
tonight's Q&A.
Angela Davis says in Leviticus 11, we
are taught what we can and cannot eat.
But how do I respond to those who say
that God blessed everything so we can
eat what we want?
>> All right. Well, first of all, we know
that you cannot eat what you want
because God is the one that set up
what's called a dietary law. And
sometimes once you read the pages and
the words that are written in the Bible
and they still don't want to adhere to
it, then you just have to wait and hope
that God opens their eyes. But we're
going to read it to them, too, and see
if this is of some help to them. So, we
will not go into Leviticus the whole
chapter, but let's go into that
Leviticus 11, brother James. And let's
pick it up at that verse one. And this
is the Lord saying to Moses and to Aaron
what he wants his dietary law to be. So,
let's read directly out of the Bible. Go
ahead, my brother.
And the Lord spake unto Moses and to
Aaron, saying unto them, Speak unto the
children of Israel, saying, These are
the beasts which you shall eat among all
the beasts that are on the earth.
>> Uhhuh. So it said here that out of all
the beasts, these are the ones that the
Lord said that you can eat that's on the
earth. Go ahead.
whatsoever part the hoof and is
clovenfooted and cheweth the cud among
the beasts that shall ye eat. Uh-huh.
>> Nevertheless, these shall ye not eat of
them that chew the cud or of them that
divide the hoof as the camel because he
cheweth the cud but divideth not the
hoof. He is unclean.
>> Go ahead.
>> He is unclean unto you.
>> So Lord is saying here that these are
the beasts that he wants you to eat
that's on the earth. And then he goes
into the ones that you shall not eat.
Skip down and let's take pig off the
table right now. Verse seven.
>> And the swan though he divide the hoof
and be clovenfooted yet he chewth not
the cud, he is unclean to you. So the
pig automatically cannot eat him, no
part of him because even though he
divide the hoof and and his clothing and
footed, yet he cheweth not the cud
because he will eat anything. So you
cannot eat the pig. Skip down to verse
nine and go ahead and read, brother.
Let's get into what's in the waters.
These shall ye eat of all that are in
the waters. Whatsoever hath fins and
scales in the waters, in the seas and in
the rivers, them shall ye eat.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And all that have not fins and scales in
the seas and in the rivers, of all that
move in the waters, and of any living
thing which is in the waters, they shall
be an abomination unto you. So Lord is
letting you know that they have to have
fins and scales if they come out of the
seas or the lakes or the rivers. That is
the only thing that the Lord wants us to
eat when it comes. It has to have fins
and scales. So no catfish, no lobster,
no shrimp. All of those you cannot eat
because they do not have fins and
scales. Skip down, brother, and pick it
up at that verse 13.
And these are they which ye shall have
an abomination among the fowls. They
shall not be eaten. They are an
abomination. The eagle and the oafrash
and the osprey. So those are the things
when it comes to what flies around in
the air that the Lord said that you
cannot eat. But as you go further, you
find out you can't eat the owl and the
swan and the eagle and the crow and all
those different things. And this is the
reason that the Lord spoke this to Moses
and Aaron. Skip down to verse 44 and
pick it up, brother. Verse 44.
For I am the Lord your God. Ye shall
therefore sanctify yourselves, and ye
shall be holy, for I am holy. Neither
shall ye defile yourselves with any
manner of creeping thing that creepeth
upon the earth.
>> So there are certain things to it. The
Lord say you can eat that creep upon the
earth like you can eat the locust. But
verse 45 here is going to tell us cuz
this is the Lord that set this dietary
law. Go ahead.
>> For I am the Lord that bringeth you up
out of the land of Egypt to be your God.
Ye shall therefore be holy for I am
holy.
>> Uhhuh. This is the law of the beast and
of the foul and of every living creature
that moveth in the waters and of every
creature that creepeth upon the earth.
>> Yes.
>> To make a difference between the unclean
and the clean and between the beasts
that may be eaten and the beasts that
may not be eaten. So Lord said he wants
to make a difference between the unclean
and the clean and the beasts that you
shall eat and the ones that you cannot
eat. So Lord is separating the people
that following him and that believe in
him because the ones that follow him,
they follow his dietary law that he has
here in Leviticus the 11th chapter and
also you can go into Deuteronomy the
14th and it would tell you more of the
beasts that you shall not eat. So this
is according to what thus says the Lord.
And this is what the Lord requires of us
when it comes to keeping his dietary
law.
And that's all I got.
All right. And we hope that that
answered your question and we gonna move
on to our next one.
>> Yes. Moving on. Time out. Houston says,
"If Satan and demons can't be killed
because they are spiritual beings, then
why was Jesus also a spiritual being
able to take on flesh and be killed?
Couldn't God also make Satan flesh and
destroy him?"
>> Brother Julius, what do the scriptures
say about that?
The scripture says that by one man sin
entered into the world and death by sin.
So death fell upon all men. The wages of
sin is death.
>> Yeah.
>> So let's go to see why why didn't God
why why did God have to come in the
flesh? He had to come in the flesh. The
devils and all the angels. He wasn't he
didn't create a devil. He became the
devil. He created Lucifer. All the
angels of God servant. But they were
free moral agents. And those that uh uh
transgress they sin and they spirit
beings. You cannot kill a spirit being.
That's why Matthew 25 said and 41 said
the lake of fire was made for Satan and
his angels and everybody that's
rebellious. Let's go to Hebrews 9 the 2
chapter and let's look at brother James
Hebrews 2 and let's read why Jesus had
to come in the flesh. Remember Satan
deceived Adam uh deceived the woman not
the man
but through the man sin came into the
world and death. Hebrews 2 and we going
to read verse 9 and 10 and then we'll
skip. Go ahead brother.
>> But we see Jesus who was made a little
lower than the angels for the suffering
of death.
>> That's why he had to come in a a flesh
and blood body when he came. You can't
kill God. So he reduced himself and a
body was prepared for him and he came
through Mary in the flesh. For what
reason, James? Go ahead.
>> Crowned with glory and honor that he by
the grace of God should taste death for
every man.
>> Go ahead. for it became him for whom are
all things and by whom are all things
and bringing my sons unto glory to make
the captain of their salvation perfect
through sufferings.
>> So the plan of God was to create this
man in his image and his likeness and
eventually make him God so that he could
be a part of the God family. Skip down
to verse 14 and 15. Go ahead. For as
much then as the children are partakers
of flesh and blood, he als he also
himself likewise took part of the same
manner that through death he might
destroy him that had the power of death
that is the devil. And that's what Satan
that devil had the power over death
because how through deception he would
deceive you. You would sin against God
and the wages of sin is death. So this
is why Jesus had to come. Continue at
15.
>> And deliver them who through fear of
death were all their lifetimes subject
to bondage.
>> So that's why uh by one man fled s uh by
one man sin into the world, the second
Adam, which is Jesus had to come and
take away death off the table so you
could have a right
to the tree of life so you could be a
part of the God family. Let's go to uh 1
John 3:8.
1 John 3:8.
God
made him a Lucifer, a spirit being. He
rebelled. He became the devil. And hey,
he knew right from wrong. We learning
right from wrong. Now we know right from
wrong. So if we sin against God and and
and uh we died our sin without
repenting, you're going to be joining
Satan in the lake of fire. Hebrews, I'm
sorry, um 1 John 3 and just one verse,
verse 8. Go ahead. He that committh sin
is of the devil. For the devil sinnth
from the beginning. For this purpose the
son of God was manifested
that he might destroy the works of the
devil.
>> And that's what we read in Hebrews the
second chapter. Jesus had to come and be
uh in a flesh and blood body. You can't
kill God but you can kill flesh. So he
had to come in a flesh and blood body to
redeem or salvage this man so that he
could put him back on track to be a part
of the God family. I hope that helped.
So to make Satan a flesh and blood to
kill him. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
John 3 and 6 tell you that which is
spirit is spirit and that which is flesh
is flesh. So he's not the god of the
dead. He's the God of the living. So
therefore, everybody's going to live.
Even that came out the grave, they going
to live. It's just a matter where you
going to be. You going to be a spirit
being in the kingdom of God, the right
side of it, or in the lake of fire,
which will be also in the kingdom of
God, the wrong side of it. I hope that
helped.
>> Yeah. Can I grab
the thing about you saying God, how can
God why can't God just make Satan flesh
and kill him? If he had, then he still
would have rose. He still would have
rose back up. Sure, Jesus killed in the
flesh, but he rose again. So, uh, when
he came in the flesh and was killed,
that was just a a a temporary condition.
If he made Satan flesh, then
he would have had to raise him up again
because uh uh uh flesh is a temporary
condition. So he still wouldn't
accomplish nothing.
>> And Jesus didn't die and stay in the
flesh and stay dead. He rose again.
>> And tell y'all so that uh uh uh uh that
uh everybody's going to rise from the
everlasting life. That's on the good
side of the kingdom or some to
everlasting shame and contempt. So if he
had made f Satan flesh and killed him,
he still would have rose again. So he
still have this being that he have to do
something with.
That's all I have to say.
>> Thank you guest call.
>> All right. Thank you for that. Hope that
answered your question. As we move on to
our next question,
>> next one. Serena Kendall says, "I know
someone that has been in a long-term
relationship with her first cousin, and
they will marry soon. Is this acceptable
in God's sight since it does not
specifically list cousins in the
scripture?"
>> All right, guess call. They talking
about cousins in marriage.
But I have a situation that didn't seem
to bother God.
Let's go into Joshua the 15th chapter
and we're going to read verses 16 and
17.
Okay. Joshua the 15th chapter 16 and 17.
Correct sir?
>> That's correct.
>> Okay. It says, "And Caleb, I'm sorry, 15
and uh
and Caleb said, he that smiteth her jazz
sephar, and taketh it, to him will I
give my daughter to wife." And Athen the
son of Canaz, the brother of Caleb, took
it, and gave him Asha, his daughter, to
wife.
Okay, there's where uh uh two cousins
got married right there.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right, so we're going to leave it
right there as we continue to move on
with our next question.
>> Next question. MJ asks, "Is there a
specific number of chapters of the Bible
we should read daily?"
So, out of the whole Bible, is there a
specific number of chapters that you
should read daily? Brother Dre, what you
say?
>> No,
there's not a specific number of
chapters that we should read. Let's go
to First Timothy, the fourth chapter. 1
Timothy 4.
We going to read verse 13.
And we'll skip from there.
Go ahead, brother, when you get it.
>> Okay. It says, "Till I come, give
attendance to reading, to exhortation,
to doctrine."
>> So, we should give some attendance to
reading, to exhortation, and to
doctrine. Skip down to 15.
>> Meditate upon these things. Give thyself
wholly to them, that thy profiting may
appear to all.
>> Mhm. Take heed unto thyself and into the
doctrine. Continue in them. For in doing
this, thou shalt both save thyself and
them that hear thee.
>> Yes, sir. So, uh, Psalm 1 tell you to
meditate on his law day and night,
>> and you be like a tree planted by the
rivers of waters.
>> Let's go to Joshua the first chapter.
Joshua, the first chapter, and we going
to read one verse there.
Joshua the 1st chapter verse 8. Go ahead
brother.
>> Okay. Joshua 1 and verse 8 says,
"This book of the law shall not depart
out of thy mouth, but thou shalt
meditate therein day and night, that
thou mayest observe to do according to
all that is written therein." For then
thou shalt make the way thy way
prosperous, and then thou shalt have
good success.
>> Absolutely. So, we should read and
meditate on his word.
But as far as how many chapters we
should read today, I haven't read that
in the book. That's all I got to say. Go
ahead.
>> All right. Yes, sir. And hey, like the
Lord say too, Brother Dre, study to show
thyself approved. That's right. That's
what
>> it say in sec in in second Timothy 2 and
15. Study to show thyself approved.
>> Yes, sir.
>> All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we continue to move on to our next
question,
>> moving on. Red Wolf says, "If your
immediate family member, mother,
brother, etc. die and the funeral is on
the Sabbath day. Do you go or not?
Scripture says, "Let the dead bury their
dead and always keep your garment
white."
>> So immediate family member passes away.
Do you go or not? Because they seem to
think that let the dead bury they dead
ties into that guest caller.
Well, why don't we go into Matthew the
18th chapter and read verse 21 and 22
and have a look at it.
>> Yep.
>> Okay.
Matthew 18 21
>> 8.
>> Oh, Matthews 8. Sorry about that, sir.
>> Let me get there.
Matthew 8 and 21 and 22
says, "And another of his disciples said
unto him, Lord, suffer me first to go
and bury my father." But Jesus said unto
him, "Follow me, and let the dead bury
the dead."
Now that scripture cannot be used uh for
that on the Sabbath because there's
nowhere in that scripture that said what
Jesus what what it was the Sabbath day
just use that for face value and then
they would be saying well you know uh
you shouldn't uh uh man of God shouldn't
uh deal with no funeral but when it get
to uncleanliness they start the book
tell you if you touch a dead body then
uh uh you're unclean.
But the whole thing is uh there is no
but if you don't touch the whole body I
don't see nothing in the Bible that said
that you cannot go to a loved one's
funeral on the Sabbath day cuz it
certainly ain't no pleasure.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right, we hope that answered your
question as we continue to keep moving
>> moving on. 9 says in Isaiah 65
17 and 20 it says in the new heaven and
earth people still die but Revelations
21 verse4 says no more death how can
both be describing the same time period
>> all right shed some light on these both
times brother Jerome
Um they're they're not the same time
period. I know it sound like it is, but
it's not. Um Isaiah 65 is the son's
kingdom and Revelations 21 and the
father's kingdom. But let's go to the
verse that you gave in the question. Uh
Isaiah 65
verse 17 and verse 20.
When you get it, go ahead and read.
>> Okay. For behold, I create new heavens
and a new earth, and the former shall
not be remembered, nor come into mind.
Verse 20 says, "There shall be no more
thence an infant of days, nor an old man
that hath not filled his days. For the
child shall die a 100 years old, but the
sinner be 100 years old, be accursed."
>> Yeah. So, yeah. in the son's kingdom, he
going he going it's going to be a
creation of new heavens and a new earth.
But when the father's kingdom get here,
he going he going to do it again. It's
going to be another change, you know.
And I'm going to point out some of these
changes. Take for instance when in the
in the u son's kingdom, it's going to be
a river that come from under his throne
under under his temple where he going to
reside and it's going to heal all the
waters. It's going to heal the seas.
Okay, that's not going to happen in the
father's kingdom. Why? Cuz I'm going to
read to you that it ain't even going to
be any seeds in the father's kingdom.
So, that's a change right there. Okay.
Uh and as you pointed out, they there's
going to be some spirit beings in the
son's kingdom and some flesh and blood
beings in the son's kingdom. And flesh
and blood and they don't, you know, they
they die cuz flesh don't live forever.
Okay? But in the father's kingdom, as
you know, there ain't going to be no
more death. Okay? So, that's a change.
All right? And I'm going to point out
another change. But, uh, let's go let's
go to that Revelations cuz you had that
Revelations 21 and 4. So, let's read
that.
>> Okay. It says, "And God shall wipe away
all tears from their eyes, and there
shall be no more death, neither sorrow
nor crying, neither shall there be any
more pain, for the former things are
passed away."
Yeah. So, as you establish in that,
Isaiah, flesh and blood going to be
there. So, you going to have some death.
They'll live long lives, but they still
subject to die cuz they can't live uh to
be a thousand. They can live to be 8 900
years but not a thousand. Okay? But in
the father's kingdom ain't going to be
no more death. Now let me tell you
something else that's in the father's
kingdom that's not in the son's kingdom.
Uh read that first verse in that
Revelations 21.
>> And I saw a new heaven and a new earth
for the first heaven and the first earth
were passed away
>> and there was no more sea. Now, I
established earlier, but in the son's
kingdom, it's going to be seized, but
not in the father's kingdom. So, that's
a change right there. Okay? What else is
in the father's kingdom that's not in
the son's kingdom? Read that second
verse.
And I, John, saw the holy city, New
Jerusalem, coming down from God out of
heaven, prepared as a bride adorned for
her husband.
>> Yeah. So, New Jerusalem ain't going to
be in the son's kingdom.
It's going to be in the father's kingdom
though cuz you know that's you know
that's the completion right there. You
know when the father's kingdom come he
bringing that city down and he going to
be in it the father himself
>> you know that ain't taking place in the
uh son's kingdom and then also in
revelations 20 when you had that
judgment day said heaven and earth fled
away there was some changes made. So
yeah, it's going to be changes made in
the son's kingdom with the heavens and
the earth. And then it's going to happen
again when the father's kingdom is
established in that 21st chapter of
Revelations. That's all I got on.
>> Yes, sir. That is our ultimate goal to
get there. All right. Hope that answered
your question as we move on to our next
one.
>> Moving on. Kylie Parker asks, "Are there
any scriptures that support or against
the idea that Satan can read minds?"
>> Are there any scriptures for or against
that Satan can read minds? Guest caller,
you with us? Guest caller?
Okay. Can you hear me now?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Yeah. You know, you have a scripture
that's look like look like uh he can and
you have a scripture that look like he
can't. You know, Gabriel was delivering
a message and uh uh uh
they didn't want to, I guess, wanted to
find out about it.
Let's go into Daniel's 10
and uh we going to read verses uh 12 and
13. Let's see.
Mhm.
>> Okay.
>> That's Daniel 10 12 and 13. It says,
"Then said he unto me, fear not, Daniel,
for from the first day that thou didest
set thine heart to understand, and to
chasten thyself before thy God, thy
words were heard, and I am come for thy
words." But the prince of the kingdom of
Persia withtood me one and 20 days. But
lo, Michael, one of the chief princes,
came to help me, and I remained there
with the kings of Persia.
Now, and uh uh
that message
says later on, you know, that uh uh
maybe you can look at it right quick.
They said only uh uh Gabriel the chief
prince you know uh
understand this with me. Let me see
where it is. I
>> think it's the same chapter verse 21.
>> Verse 21.
>> I think so.
But I will show thee that that which is
noted in the scripture of truth. And
there is none that holdeth with me in
these things but Michael your prince.
Now this tell me that Gabriel that that
uh Gabriel have a message for Daniel and
u Satan engaged him and held him up for
three weeks.
But then Micah come and pull Satan up
off up off Gabriel. It says here that uh
uh uh that only Michael you know that I
will show thee that uh which is noted in
the scripture of truth. There is none
that holdeth with me and these things
but Michael your oppressed. So that mean
that Satan was trying to find out and he
didn't know the message that God had
sent to Daniel.
>> Didn't know. But then
but then as one is pro
is is con say he couldn't do it had he
not done it then then Gab then Micah
wouldn't have been the only one that
knew what God had sent by Gabel. You see
that?
>> Yep.
>> But then you have something else. Now,
let's go into Ezekiel
28th chapter
and we going to start reading at verse
one.
Okay. Ezekiel 28:1 says, "The word of
the Lord came again unto me, saying, son
of man, say unto the prince of Tyrus,
thus sayeth the Lord God, because thine
heart is lifted up, and thou has said, I
am a God. I sit in the seat of God, in
the midst of the seas, yet thou art a
man and not God." though that
>> even even though the Lord said yet th
man and not God, we know that he's
talking about the prince that's behind
the prince. Okay?
>> Look, look what he said. Go ahead.
>> Though thou set thine heart as the heart
of God.
>> Behold, thou art wiser than Daniel,
there is no secret that they can hide
from thee.
Now when you look at that you see wise
and Samuel that there's no secret they
can hide from you. That mean that
whatever it is then he can read your
mind and get it. But over here we find
out that he was trying to get the
message that God was sending to Daniel.
So you have a pro and a con there. But
the one thing I noticed about this whole
thing, neither one of these have any
kind of salvation tenaces to it. Now I
would suggest that uh that's one of the
things that we have to wait until the
Lord come to find out. But the biggest
thing you need to be concerned with is
how to get salvation. That's all I have
to say.
>> All right. And sir, salvation is written
in the pages of the book. All right.
Let's move on to our next question.
Sister Deborah with a time check.
>> Yes. The time is 8:04. Uh, time out.
Houston says, "If Abraham kept God's
law, but he married his halfsister." And
Moses law says, "Cursed is anyone who
sleep with his sister." And that's in
Deuteronomy 27 verse 22. Was Abraham
really keeping the same laws as Moses?
Brother Julia, shed some light.
>> You know, I I looked at this question
real good and it's almost as if someone
is trying to find a fault.
I'm going to answer the question this
way right here. But we're going to do a
comparison with Abraham and Moses.
Because Abraham is called the father of
the faithful. Let's go to Matthew. I'm
I'm going to take a different approach
to this. Let's go to Matthew the 19th
chapter. And this how I'mma answer this
question.
Matthew 19 and we verse start at verse
16 James.
>> Okay. Matthew 19 and 16 says, "And
behold, one came and said unto him, good
master, what good thing shall I do that
I may have eternal life?"
>> Now, that's what we looking for. That's
what all the patriarchs are looking for,
and that's what we're looking for. Go
ahead, brother.
>> And he said unto him, why callst thou me
good? There is none good but one, that
is God. But if thou will enter into
life, keep the commandments.
>> If you want eternal life, keep the
commandments. Now, let's go to Abraham.
Let's see if Abraham kept the
commandments. I think that's a better
question. Did Abraham keep the
commandments?
Let's go to Genesis the 26th chapter.
Jam, we gonna read verses three and
five. Genesis 26 3 and five. Stop.
Matter of fact, start at verse one
because this
>> this is Isaac now, Abraham's son, Isaac.
>> And look, go ahead.
>> Pick it up at pick it up at verse two.
>> Okay.
>> And the Lord appeared unto him and said,
"Go not down into Egypt. Dwell in the
land which I shall tell thee of." Verse
one let you know it's talking about
Abraham's son Isaac. Go ahead.
>> So join in this land and I will be with
thee and will bless thee for unto thee
and unto thy seed. I will give all these
countries and I will perform the oath
which I swear unto Abraham thy father.
>> Verse five.
>> Because that Abraham obeyed my voice.
Abraham obeyed my voice
>> and kept my charge.
>> And what else?
>> My commandments.
>> Oh, in order to enter into life, you
must keep the commandments. Right.
>> Correct.
>> Continue.
>> My statutes and my laws.
>> Now, let's go to Deuteronomy the 34th
chapter and let's look at Moses.
cuz we know Moses
who was called the lawgiver
kept the commandments of God and
although he didn't circumcise his uh son
his wife circumcised it circumcised his
son but Moses
let's look at him here mo uh Deuteronomy
34 Deuteronomy 34 and let's pick this up
at verse 5 and 6 read verse 5 and six
>> so Moses the servant of the Lord died
there in the land of Moab
according to the word of the Lord.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And he buried him in a valley in the
land of Moab over against Beth Piorore,
but no man north of his supplica until
this day. Now Moses died. Let's go one
more place. Let's go to Matthew the 8th
chapter because we know that Moses
is going to be in the kingdom.
Matthew chapter 8. And I got one verse
there. Matthew 8. And when you get it,
Brother James, read verse 11. Look what
Jesus said.
>> And I
go ahead.
>> And I say unto you that many shall come
from the east and west, and shall sit
down with Abraham and Isaac and Jacob in
the kingdom of heaven. So now we know
that everybody that's in the first
resurrection is going to be in Jesus'
kingdom and going to come on into the
father's kingdom including Moses.
So I don't worry about because Abraham
married his sister.
That was the plan of God. Whole bunch of
people married each other uh in the days
of Noah and they had to repopulate the
earth in the days of uh in the days of
uh Shim, Ham, and Japheth. They had to
do the same thing and repopulate the
earth. But at when the when it got to a
certain point, the Lord cut it off. My
biggest point is, is Abraham going to be
in the kingdom? Yes. Is Moses going to
be in the kingdom? Yes. That's all I got
for that answer.
>> All right. Hope that answered your
question as we move on to our next one.
>> Yes. Moving on. Titha Wooy asks, "Is
Mechisedc
priesthood
greater than Aaron or those under the
law?" Did Jesus get his priesthood from
him? Is Mechisedc the progenitor of
Jesus?
>> Yes, caller. Can you please share some
light on that question?
But the whole thing is man she cannot be
progenative of anybody because he was a
spirit being.
>> Yes.
>> So he's of Jesus. He is Jesus
and Jesus is Melisedc. Let's go into and
and and and is the uh Melchisedc
priesthood greater than Levi than
Leviticus? Let's go into Hebrews the 7th
chapter and and and we're going to have
to do some skipping here. Okay, we going
to go to Hebrews chapter 2 uh chapter 7
rather. And uh first thing we going to
do is is uh uh
we going to read
from verses 1 7 1 uh one uh verse one
and through 4.
>> Hebrews 7 verse 1-4.
Okay. Hebrews 7:1 says, "For this
Melchisedc, king of Salem, prince of the
most high God, who met Abraham,
returning from the slaughter of the
kings, and blessed him,
to whom also Abraham gave a tenth part
of all, first being by interpretation
king of righteousness, and after that
also king of Salem, which is king of
peace,
without father,
without mother, without descent, having
neither beginning of days, nor end of
life, but made like unto the son of God,
abideth a priest continually.
>> Now, let you know, this let you know
right here, Mechisedc, you know, he
didn't have no mother, no father, no
beginning, no end. And he uh uh and he
abided a priest continually. He couldn't
die. Go ahead and read.
>> Now consider how great this man was unto
whom even the patriarch Abraham gave the
tenth of the spoils.
>> It called him man. But we know man have
a beginning and he have an end.
But he said this guy made like unto the
son of God that have no beginning and no
end. Now skip down to verse 9 and read 9
through 11.
And as I may,
verse verse 9 through 11 says, "And as I
may so say, Levi also who receiveth
tithes paid tithes in Abraham.
For he for he was yet in the loins of
his father when Mechqueisedc met him. If
therefore perfection were by the
Levitical priesthood, for under it the
people received the law, what further
need was there that another priest
should rise after the order of
Mechqueisedc and not be called after the
order of Aaron.
>> Now you see what it says here. Look, uh
uh Levi was in Abraham's lawn when he
paid tithe to Mechisedc.
So now and said too, if uh uh uh if
perfection had been by Levitical
priesthood, then what need would there
have been for another priest to rise up?
What verse was that?
>> That was verse 11.
>> Okay, skip down to verse 22
and read 22-2.
Okay, it says by so much was Jesus made
assurityity of a better testament and
they
>> said it better testament. Go ahead and
read
>> and they truly were many priests because
they were not suffered to continue by
reason of death.
>> Uhhuh. But this man, because he was
continued ever, continuth ever, have an
unchangeable priesthood,
>> where wherefore he is able also to save
them to the utmost that come unto God by
him, seeing he ever liveth to make
intercession for them.
>> Different. know Levitical priesthood,
you know, that dealt with animal
sacrifice, the law of animal sacrifice.
There were many in there because uh they
died.
But Melissa didn't show he came he came
and he came in the flesh in the name of
Jesus. He died. But then uh uh uh he was
rose again and he picked up his own
priesthood. His same priesthood.
>> See, because it said it is unchangeable.
So if it is unchangeable, how can Jesus
being somebody else take over from
Mechised that?
>> All right,
>> you finished that, right?
>> Yes, sir.
>> Let's go to one other place. Let's go
into Hebrews the 10th chapter.
Hebrews chapter 10
and we going and uh uh uh
read from verse 11
through 14.
>> Okay. Hebrews 10 verse 11-14 says, "And
every priest standeth daily ministering
and offering oftent times the same
sacrifices which can never take away
sins."
>> These priests here are Levites. Okay.
First thing is they they often couldn't
take away sin. Go ahead and read. But
this man, after he had offered one
sacrifice for sins forever, sat down on
the right hand of God.
From henceforth expecting till his
enemies be made his foottool.
For by one offering he had perfected
forever them that are sanctified.
>> So the whole thing is his offering
do it forever.
So you can get the uh uh uh uh uh and
you and that's where you get salvation
under. But uh the Levitical priesthood
could not remove sin.
Therefore, it was really an exercise in
futility.
So what it is Melchisedc offered eternal
life.
Levi offered animal sacrifice which
could never remove sin. So yeah,
Mechisedc
priesthood is greater than Levi's. And
again I said Mechisedc and Jesus is one
and the same because you cannot replace
a priest until he die. That's why they
said was many Levite because by reason
of death. Isn't that what it read?
>> So if you can't die then you can't
change priesthood. Jesus and Melchisedc
same people and they're greater than
Levi because Mechisedc
uh uh order Mechisedc priesthood to give
you eternal life.
Bitical priesthood will get you the lake
of fire cuz they could not remove sin.
That's all I have to say.
>> That's right. Yep. So that's your
answer. Mechqueisedc
is greater than the priesthood and
Aaron.
So, thank you for that question. Hope it
answered your question. As we move on to
our next question,
>> moving on. Uh, Sister Audrey B says,
"Since the white man made the calendar,
how do we know which day is actually the
seventh day? If Monday is the first day
of the week, doesn't that make Sunday
the seventh day according to the
calendar?" Now,
>> I don't know about that, brother Julius.
What you say?
>> Absolutely not. First of all, let's make
a correction. The white man did not make
the calendar. Let's see who made the
calendar. Let's go to Genesis chapter 1,
Brother James.
>> Genesis chapter one. We're going to read
verses 1 to5.
>> When you get it, go ahead, brother. In
the beginning, God created the heaven
and the earth. And the earth was without
form and void, and darkness was upon the
face of the deep, and the spirit of God
moved upon the face of the waters. And
God said, "Let there be light, and there
was light. And God saw the light, that
it was good." And God divided the light
from the darkness. And God called the
light day, and the darkness he called
night, and the evening and the morning
were the first day.
>> You could read the whole chapter on your
own. You could read the whole chapter on
your own. The Lord created everything in
six days. And let's look at this seventh
day. The whole world operates on a
seven-day week cycle. Now, in Europe,
they have made some changes. The white
man changed the or tried to change the
calendar. Genesis chapter 2 and verse 1.
Thus the heavens and the earth were
finished and all the host of them.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And on the seventh day God ended his
work which he had made. And he rested on
the seventh day from all his work which
he had made.
>> And so and and what I said verse three.
And God blessed the seventh day and
sanctified it, because that in it he had
rested from all his work which God
created and made. There was not a man
until the ground when the Lord created
the heavens and the earth. So he day one
to day seven he numbered his days and he
named the seventh day and called it the
Sabbath which means rest. Now let's look
at what happened. Let's go to uh Daniel
the 7th chapter.
Daniel chapter 7.
Daniel chapter 7. Because the whole
world at one time kept the Sabbath day.
Somebody came along and changed it.
Daniel 7 and read verse 25. My brother.
Daniel 7 and read verse 25. This is all
about the little horn which is the head
of the Catholic Church.
Daniel 7 and look what the book said
that he was going to do in this uh uh we
in the fourth beast which uh in these
last times. Now we come down to the 10
toes of Daniel, the European Union,
Western Europe. Daniel 7:25. Go ahead.
And he shall speak great words against
the most high, and shall wear out the
saints of the most high, and think to
change times and laws, and they shall be
given into his hand until a time, and
times, and the dividing of time. Now,
the Sabbath day is the only which is the
fourth commandment. The Catholic Church
calls it the third commandment. But in
the fourth commandment, it says it is
the only day uh commandment that start
with remember the Sabbath day and keep
it holy. The Sabbath day is a day and a
law. They shall think that change times
and a law. The Sabbath is a time and a
law. Now, let's look at what happened. I
looked it up. I knew this years ago, but
there's a book called The Converts
Catechism of Catholic Doctrine.
The Converse Catechism of Catholic
Doctrine. In page 49, it deals with the
Ten Commandments. This is a quote. I
printed this up. This is a quote. It
says, uh, what is the third commandment?
The third commandment is remember that
thou keep holy the Sabbath day. Which is
the Sabbath day? Saturday is the Sabbath
day, which is day seven. Now, why do we
observe Sunday instead of Saturday? We
observe and this is out of their
catechism. We observe Sunday instead of
Saturday because the Catholic Church and
the council of Leodysia which was 363
transferred the solity from Saturday to
Sunday. Why did the Catholic Church
substitute Sunday for Saturday? The
church substituted Sunday for Saturday
because Christ rose from the dead on a
Sunday which is not which is not true.
He rose on the seventh day and the Holy
Ghost descended upon the apostles on the
Sunday which is not true. So sisters and
brothers in 3:21
42 years earlier a Roman emperor by the
name of Constantine the first
changed the Sabbath day from the seventh
day to the first day. Sunday is the
first day of the week. That's why you
don't see Sunday money Monday too. You
see 1 through 7. God number these days
and change it in 321 AD from the se from
the seventh day to the first day. This
is why they do this in Europe. So now in
Europe in 1988 they the Switzerland
council international council came up
with ISO 8601
which ensures that daytime data can be
accurately transformed and understood
across international boundaries. So in
that's why in Europe they keep the uh
they keep Monday as the first day but
it's always been Sunday
is the first day and the Sabbath is the
s is the seventh day. That is it.
I hope that helped. Anybody else?
>> Yeah, Julius, I just want to go to one
book. Luke 4. Let's go to Luke 4 right
quick.
>> Yep.
>> Yep. pick it up at that verse 14 because
uh we have to see what Jesus did when he
came in the flesh because he said he's
the shepherd of the sheep, didn't he?
>> Yes, sir.
>> So read that 14 and then brother Julius
can close it out with that explanation.
14 through 16. Go ahead, brother.
>> And Jesus returned in the power of the
spirit into Galilee. And there went out
of fame of him through all the region
round about.
>> Mhm. And he taught in their synagogues,
being glorified of all. And he came to
Nazareth, where he had been brought up.
And as his custom was, he went into the
synagogue on the Sabbath day and stood
up for to read.
>> And in the New and also in the New
Testament, as Paul custom was, he reads
in in the synagogue every Sabbath. So
the Sabbath day is the Saturday or what
we call Saturday, but it is the seventh
day. It has always been and the whole
world at one time kept the Sabbath day
and then wrong came along and changed
it. So man didn't make the calendar. God
did
>> man changed it. But you can't change
God's laws.
>> Thank you, brother Cornell. Guest
caller. All right. Once again too, uh,
this person said that Monday is the
first day of the week. I don't know what
calendar she look at looking at. She's
not in Europe unless she's in Europe.
>> Yeah, that's what that's what they do in
Europe.
>> You're not in Europe, you're in America,
get a calendar, look at it. Today,
Sunday is the first day of the week.
>> All I have to say.
>> Yeah. So now Cornell, if you make Monday
the first day of the week, now you could
justify being Sunday being the Lord's
day, which it is not. And that's why I
went to Daniel 7:25 where the book
prophesied that they should change think
to change times and laws. But there
those of us who know our God and we know
this book, we know that the Sabbath day
is the seventh day and Sunday is the
first day of the week. Hey, brother
Cornell, can we go to one place to fully
prove what Julius and the guest car just
said? The first day is Sunday. We know
the first day ain't the Sabbath. That's
the point I want to make. And I want to
go to Matthews 28
>> to prove that.
>> Okay. M I think it's Matthews 28 and1.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah. It says in the end of the Sabbath
as it began to dawn toward the first day
of the week.
>> So, you know, the first day of the week
ain't the Sabbath.
>> That's all I wanted to say.
>> But they're working on they're working
on new calendars and new cell phones to
justify Monday being the first day of
the week.
>> Yeah. So, make sure you follow the
shepherd of the sheep, the one that
spread his blood for the sins of the
whole world. All right, sister Deborah,
we're moving on to our next one.
>> Yes, moving on. And the time is 8:28.
Valencia asks in Zechariah 1 verse 21,
are the horn angels and what part are
the Gentiles?
All right, brother Jerome.
>> Let's go read the verse. Zechariah 1 and
21.
>> It says, "Then said I, what cometh these
to do?" And he spake, saying, "These are
the horns which have scattered Judah, so
that no man did lift up his head, but
these are come to fray them, to cast out
the horns of the Gentiles, which lifted
up their own up which lifted up their
horn over the land of Judah to scatter
it."
>> It's kind of selfexplanatory.
If you look at it closely, it tells you
in that verse, the horns were the ones
that scattered
Judah. And then it tells you who those
horns were that scattered Judah. And it
told you Gentiles.
Okay, those are the horns, the horns of
the Gentiles.
Okay, so if anybody want to add
something to it, they can. That the
horns in that verse, not talking about
any place else. The horns in that verse
are Gentiles. They the ones that
scattered the Jews.
That's all I got.
>> Yeah, we know them horns deal with
Babylonian, Meo, Persian, Greek, and
Rome.
>> Yeah, good point.
>> All right. Thank you for that, brother.
As we continue to move on to our next
question.
>> Next question. Brit Brett says, "Someone
wanted to make KJV Bibles
to sell. I told him that I believe that
Bibles should be free and referred him
to the scriptures in Luke 19 45 and 46.
Was this a good reference?"
>> All right. Well, guess call it. They say
someone wanted to make KJV Bibles. It's
already a made deal. What you say?
>> Let's go to Luke 19:45 and 46 and read
it.
>> Okay. Luke 19 and45-46
says, "And he went into the temple, and
began to cast out them that sold
therein, and them that bought, saying
unto them, it is written, my house is
the house of prayer, but ye have made it
a den of thieves."
So, so the question was, was this a good
reference? The answer is no.
don't have nothing to do with uh uh what
they buying and selling is what the the
church is dealing dealing with
everything inside of it but the word of
God. But as far the Bible is concerned,
look all Bibles are made by somebody
and the people that made them sold them.
So if this person want to make some King
James version and make them just make
them correctly and sell them, then it's
a business that don't have nothing with
him uh uh have nothing with the
corruption that's going on into the
church now
cuz all the Bibles we have everyone
somebody bought them. So if you want to
go into the business, why not? And when
it come to uh uh uh where Jesus cast out
the money changers and all that and the
house become God's house become robbers
and thieves then that is this people
that's preaching and uh uh uh and uh and
they use the church to get money instead
of spread the word of God. That's all I
have to say.
>> All right, we're going to move on to our
next question.
>> Next one. She also asks, "Can a man that
is not a naturalb born Israelite but
converted and follows the true gospel of
the Israel of God become a pastor,
meaning a white person and or another
nationality?"
>> Yes. Caller.
Well,
I said what we need to do about that
is look at the protocol. The Lord is the
one that set the protocol. Let's go to
Isaiah 43rd chapter and read verse 10
and 12
and we're going to skip down to 21.
>> Okay. Isaiah 43
10 and 10. Verse says, "Ye are my
witnesses, sayaeth the Lord, and my
servant whom I have chosen, that ye may
know and believe me, and understand that
I am he. Before me there was no God
formed, neither shall there be after
me."
>> Go ahead.
>> Verse verse uh You want me to read 11 as
well, or just jump to 12?
>> Uh-uh. Read right on through.
>> 12. Okay. I even I am the Lord and
beside me there is no savior. I have
declared and have saved. I have showed
when there was no stranger God, no
strange God among you. Therefore, ye are
my witnesses, sayeth the Lord, that I am
God.
>> So, Israel is the Lord's witnesses. Get
down to 21 and read it.
This people have I formed for myself.
They shall show forth my praise.
>> Now, it's Israel here.
>> That's pretty specific, isn't it?
>> Yes.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay. Well, then let's go uh uh uh
let's go into Romans
3 chapter
and we going to read verses one and two.
Okay. Romans the 3 chapter verses 1 and
2 says, "What advantage then hath the
Jew? Or what profit is there of
circumcision?
Much every way chiefly because that unto
them were committed the oracles of God."
>> So the oracles of God was committed to
Israel. It's all that simple.
Let's go to Acts 10th chapter.
Read verse 1-5.
>> Okay.
Acts 10 verses 1-5 says there was a
certain man in in Ceras called Cornelius
a centurion of the band called the
Italian band a devout man and one that
feared God with all his house and which
gave much arms to the people and prayed
to God always.
He was he saw in a vision evidently
about the ninth hour of the day an angel
of God coming into him and saying unto
him Cornelius. And when he looked unto
him, he was afraid and said, "What is
it, Lord?" And he said unto him, "Thy
prayers and thy arms are come up for
memorial before God." And now send men
to Japa and call for one Simon whose
surname is Peter.
>> Go ahead.
>> He lodges with one Simon a tanner whose
house is by the seaside. He shall tell
thee what thou ought to do.
>> Now Canadian was a devout man. It looked
like uh uh uh that angel could have
taught him, but the angel didn't do
that. He sent him to Peter.
Now being that this man was devout, look
like the Lord should could have used
this Gentile to send him to the rest of
the Gentiles. But he didn't do that. He
used Paul and made him the apostle to
the Gentiles. Paul the Hebrew Israelite.
So now that is the protocol. If a
Gentile should get up and want to be a
pastor and been taught by the Israel and
God, then I say
that's between him and God. But the
protocol is the protocol and we can't
change. And the reason I say that
because look at all those Gentiles that
Paul taught.
Now what happened after 7 AD when the uh
uh Romans took down Judah and scattered
us all over the Mediterranean and
eventually to America and all over. What
happened to the word of God? It fell to
the ground. All of a sudden people are
teaching going to heaven. People saying
you can eat pork. People are saying the
first day of the week is the Lord's time
of day. People say you got people in
heaven looking down. All this kind of
talk come from the Gentiles and the
Gentiles were not going into captivity.
Why is it that these Gentiles went back
to sleep? That is a question that need
to be answered.
But as me,
the Lord set the protocol and I'm not
going to deviate from it. That's all I
have to say.
>> Right? Lord even say you only have I
known that all the families of the earth
All right.
>> Okay. Hope that answered your question
as we move on to our next one.
>> Next one. Jalia says, "My granddaughter
asked me about getting a tattoo and the
meaning of Leviticus 19 verse 28. Could
you please help us understand through
scriptures,
>> brother Dre? Help their understanding.
>> Yes, sir. Let's go to Leviticus 19 and
we're going to read verses uh we're
going to read that verse 28. Go ahead,
brother. When you get it,
>> ye shall not make any cutings into your
flesh for the dead, nor print any marks
upon you. I am the Lord.
>> So notice here it says for the dead you
shall not make any cutings in your flesh
or print any marks on. And when you look
at history you find that this is
prevalent among the Aztecs, the Mayans,
the Egyptians and a lot of other people.
They did that for the dead.
They printed on their bodies. They cut
themselves.
Let's go to Deuteronomy 14 now.
Deuteronomy 14 and we going to read
verses 1 and two. Deuteronomy 14 1 and
two. Go ahead, brother.
>> Ye are the children of the Lord your
God. Ye shall not cut yourselves, nor
make any baldness between your eyes for
the dead. For thou art an holy people
unto the Lord thy God, and the Lord had
chosen thee to be a peculiar people unto
himself above all the nations that are
upon the earth. So these these are the
things that the nations did
and they did it for the dead. And notice
he keeps saying for the dead.
So, I would ask my granddaughter,
why do she want to get a tattoo? And
when you get to that question and she
gives you an answer, I'm sure you
understand a little bit more about it.
But for the dead is what the scripture
is talking about
in terms of not doing it. That's all I
got.
>> Yep. And they even say, Dre, that
tattooing your eyes and all that stuff
can cause a loss of an eye and it's
extremely dangerous because people are
getting their eyes tattooed.
>> They doing everything in terms of
marking themselves up. But uh a lot of
it, if you trace back the history of it,
you find that it is in homage to other
gods. And on your own you could read
that first kings 18 26-28
they were cutting themselves and doing
all kind of things in trying to get
their deity to acknowledge them and eat
the sacrifice.
So be just do some research. But the
scripture says for the dead.
>> Go ahead, brother. I'm done.
>> All right, brother. Thank you for that.
As we move on to our next question, as
time is ticking.
>> Yes, next question. Tomorrow Williams
asks, "Out of the 144,000 of each tribe,
does this include women and children?"
Jerome 144,000 women and children
included in there.
>> Well, let's go um where it's talking
about the 144,000
in that uh Revelations chapter 7
>> and let's pick it up at verse two and
read it to the four.
You get it? Go ahead and read.
>> Okay. It says, "And I saw another angel
ascending from the east, having the seal
of the living God, and he cried with a
loud voice to the four angels, to whom
it was given to hurt the sea, hurt the
earth and the sea,
>> saying, "Hurt not the earth, neither the
sea, nor the trees, till we have sealed
the servants of our God in their
foreheads."
And I heard the number of them which
were sealed. And they were sealed
144,000
of all the tribes of the children of
Israel.
>> Okay? Now, these 144,000 in this
chapter,
>> this is during the time of the great
tribulation. All right? And they're
going to be in a area
where the beast and the false prophet
is going to have total control, you
know. Uh and that that's mentioned in
the sixth chapter. So let's skip up to
the sixth chapter and read verse uh
seven and 8.
And when he had opened the fourth seal,
I heard the voice of the fourth beast
say, "Come and see." And I looked, and
behold, a pale horse, and his and his
name that sat on him was death, and hell
followed with him. And power was given
unto them over the fourth part of the
earth to kill with sword, and with
hunger, and with death, and with the
beast of the earth.
>> So they going to have a control over a
fourth part of the earth, the beast, and
the false prophet. And these 144,000,
they within that fourth part of earth.
So the Lord put a seal on them. Okay?
Because the Lord, he going to be pouring
out some wrath and that's associated
with the trumpets and the and the vials
that's in the book of Revelation. He
don't want them to suffer that wrath
that's associated with them trumpets and
vials. So he put a seal up to protect
them. Now,
is it the Lord just want to protect the
men, the males,
you know, that's in that fourth part of
the earth? I I don't think he just want
to protect males. I think he want to
protect u women and children that's
among these
uh Israelites that's in that fourth part
of earth. And the count is 144,000.
Okay.
And I don't think it's just men because
I don't think he want to just protect
the men. Okay. Uh,
also
I I don't want you to uh misunderstand
there's another set of 144,000 in
Revelations
um chapter 14.
Okay? And
they're not the same as the 144 in this
seventh chapter. Okay? Cuz 144 in that
14th chapter, they are males.
Okay? All of them. All right? So, it's a
different set. All right? So, let's go
to that 14th chapter and read verse one.
Then we going to skip.
>> Go ahead.
And I looked, and lo, a lamb stood on
the mount Zion, and with him 140 and
4,000, having his father's name written
in their foreheads.
>> Let's skip down and read verse four and
five.
>> These are they which were not defiled
with women, for they are virgins. These
are they which followed the Lamb,
whatsoever he goeth. These were redeemed
from among men, being the first fruits
unto God and to the lamb.
>> Mhm.
>> And in their mouth was found no guile,
for they are without fault before the
throne of God.
>> All right? Now, this said 144,000, they
were all males. Okay? And they never
slept with women. All right? That's
that's not the case with the 144,000
in uh Revelation chapter 7. That's a
different set. That's all I got.
>> Yes, sir. Good light there. As we move
on to our next question,
>> next question. Thou says, "If no one has
ever heard the father's
have heard the father, then who was the
voice in Matthew 17:E5
saying, "This is my beloved son which
Peter later confirmed in second Peter 1
17 and 18."
>> All right. Yeah. Well, no one has ever
heard the father's voice and the angels,
the holy angels represent God and they
can speak sometimes on behalf of God
because his name is written in them.
Let's go into that Matthews.
Matthews, right? Let's go in Matthews
17 what they asked about and let's read
one and two then we going to skip down
to five and six.
Matthew's this is during the
transfiguration
with Jesus and he was up there with
Peter, James, and John. Go ahead,
brother. And after six days, Jesus
taketh Peter, James, and John his
brother, and bringeth them up into a
high mountain apart, and was
transfigured before them. And his face
did shine as the sun, and his raignment
was white as the light. It had to be
some sight. Skip down and read five and
six, brother.
>> While he yet spake, behold, a bright
cloud overshadowed them, and behold, a
voice out of the cloud, which said,
"This is my beloved son, in whom I am
well pleased. Hear ye him."
>> Yeah. So, this was an angel here
speaking
during this time right here. Let's go in
uh Matthew 3 right quick. Matthew 3 and
let's read 16-1 17. And this was at
Jesus baptism.
Matthew 3
and read that verse 16 and 17. Go ahead.
And Jesus, when he was baptized, went up
straightway out of the water, and lo,
the heavens were open unto him, and he
saw the spirit of God descending like a
dove, and lightning upon him.
>> Mhm.
>> And lo, a voice from heaven, saying,
"This is my beloved son, in whom I am
well pleased."
>> So, this is an angel here, too. This was
Jesus when he was getting baptized. We
know it wasn't his voice and we know it
wasn't a father's voice either. It was
an angel. Let's go into that second
Peter they talked about and then we
going to go into that John 5. Let's go
into second Peter first. Second Peter
1 and let's pick it up at that verse 17
and 18.
Go ahead.
These Oh, second Peter 1 you said and 17
and 18. It says, "For he received from
God the Father honor and glory, where
there came such a voice to him from the
excellent glory.
>> This is my beloved son in whom I am well
pleased."
And this voice which came from heaven,
we heard, and when we were with him in
the holy mount.
>> So that was an angel there, too. And so,
let's go to last place, John five. And
this is how we know it was an angel and
not the father because a lot of people
say it was the father's voice.
John five and let's pick it up brother
at that verse 37.
John 5 and37 says and the father himself
which has sent me and hath borne witness
of me ye have neither heard his voice at
any time nor seen his shape. So we have
not heard the father's voice at any time
nor seen this shape. So we know it
wasn't the father. It was an angel
speaking the words that the father had
spoken.
>> So I want to add something to it.
>> Yes sir.
>> We actually want the scripture to say
that an angel can call down. Let's go to
Genesis 22 chapter.
and and uh uh
we're going to read verses uh uh one and
two.
Then we're going to skip now.
>> Okay. And that's that's Genesis chapter
22. Correct, sir?
>> Verse one and two. And then we're going
to skip down to 9
and read down to 12.
>> Okay. Verse one says, "And it came to
pass after these things that God did
tempt Abraham, and said unto him,
Abraham, and he said, Behold, here am
I." And he said, "Take now thy son,
thine only son Isaac, whom thou lovest,
and get thee into the land of Mariah,
and offer him there for burnt offering
upon upon one of the mountains which I
will tell thee of."
Verse 9.
>> And they came to the place which God had
told him of. And Abraham built an altar
there, and laid the wood in order, and
bound Isaac his son, and laid him on the
altar upon the wood.
And Abraham stretched forth his hand,
and took the knife to slay his son. And
the angel of the Lord called unto him
out of heaven, and said,"Abraham,
Abraham." And he said, "Here am I."
>> Mhm.
>> We can start right here. What did the
book say? Who called out of heaven?
>> The angel of the Lord called unto him
out of heaven.
>> Come down to verse 15 and read it.
>> And the angel of the Lord called unto
Abraham out of the heaven the second
time
and said,
>> Mhm.
You know, finish that verse.
>> And said, "By myself have I sworn,
sayeth the Lord, for because thou has
done this thing and has not withheld thy
son, thine only son."
>> Okay, that's enough. See,
the angel brings the message.
>> Yeah. If you don't, I guess if you don't
feel like coming to the earth, then he
will call out of heaven just like he did
in the new book. This is my beloved son.
>> It's the angel that call. That's why I
wanted to read somewhere actually show
you that the voice from heaven is the
voice of an angel calling down. That's
all that to say.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Good add-on. We needed that
there to kind of make that clear on that
final point. All right, Sister Deborah,
we're going in new territory.
>> Yes. Uh, we are now into tonight's Q&A
for Wednesday, September the 17th, 2025.
Detroit Price asks, "Can you break down
the seven spirits of God stated in
Revelation 5 verse 6?"
Revelation 5 verse 6
and they want to break down the seven
spirits. We won't have time to do that
I'm sure but we do have a lesson titled
the seven spirits of God which are one
but let's read it anyway and then let's
open it up to the panel. What's the time
check sister Deborah?
>> The time is 8:55.
>> All right. Revelation 5 and 6. And then
let's open it up to the panel. And uh
let's roll from there.
>> Revelation 5 and6 says, "And I beheld,
and lo, in the midst of the throne, and
of the four beasts, and in the midst of
the elders stood a lamb as it had been
slain, having seven horns, and seven
eyes, which are the seven spirits of
God, sent forth into all the earth.
Seven angels.
>> That's right. Now, you got got a
scripture where it says and the seven
angel that was the seven spirit that was
in his hand, it tell you that it was
seven angels.
We want to read that.
But when he turned and he saw one like a
son of man.
>> Revelation. That's Revelation 1 and 12.
>> 1 and 12.
>> Yes, sir.
>> It says, "And I turned to see the voice
that spake with me. And being turned, I
saw seven golden candlesticks."
And in verse 13 says, "In the midst of
the seven candlesticks, one like unto
the son of man clothe with a garment
down to the foot and gert about the paps
with the golden girdle."
>> I want to keep finding out he had seven
stars in his hand which are angels.
>> That's verse 20.
>> Verse 16.
>> Verse 16,
>> right?
>> It mentions the seven stars.
And he had in his right hand seven
stars, and out of his mouth went a sharp
two-edged sword, and his countenance was
as the sun shineest in his strength.
Now, now verse uh verse 20,
>> the mystery of the seven stars which
thou sawest in my right hand, and the
seven golden candlesticks, the seven
stars are the angels of the seven
churches, and the seven candlesticks
which thou saw are the seven churches.
>> Okay, the angels are spirits. Let's go
into Hebrews the first chapter.
Hebrews
chapter one
and let's
see
let's go
uh uh
>> make of it angel spirits.
>> Yeah. Got it in verse six.
And again, when he bringeth into the
first begotten into the world, he saith,
and let all the angels of God worship
him. And of the angels he saith, who
maketh his angels spirits, and his
ministers a flame of fire?
>> So, who maketh his angels spirits? Now,
skip now to uh verse 12. Read 12 and 13.
And as a vesture shalt thou fold them
up, and they shall be changed.
>> 12 and 13. That's
>> right. That
>> Hebrews 1 and that was verse 12. You
want me to go 13 and 14?
>> 14. I'm sorry.
>> Okay.
But to which of the angels saith he at
any time, sit on my right hand until I
make thine enemies thy foottool?
Are they not all ministering spirits
sent forth to minister for them who
shall be heirs of salvation?
>> Now, so these seven spirit are seven
angels and the Lord sent these angels to
and for the earth.
Keep eye on us. So that's all. Ain't no
great breakdown. They they they are all
the all the angels are spirits. Those
particular seven
are spirits also.
And the ones that follow uh and the ones
that didn't follow Satan are holy
spirits.
And the ones that follow Satan are
unclean spirit or demon or devils.
>> So the seven spirit are seven angels.
That's all I have to say.
>> All right. We hope that answered your
question, sister Deborah, as we go to
our final question of the evening.
>> All right, the final question. Uh
Shanquilla A Joby asks,
"Can you explain John 13 verses 26 and
when Jesus says to deny yourself and
follow him?"
in Matthew 16 verse 24.
Does that imply that dark forces can
assess your bodies and use us for their
own purposes?
So the first is John 13 26 and 27.
He wants you to explain
when Jesus says to deny yourself and
follow him.
All right, let's go to John 13.
And I don't see anything about deny
thyself in there, but read that verse,
brother. Them two verse, John 13:26 and
27, right, devil?
>> Yes.
>> Go ahead, brother. that says, "Jesus
answered, he it is to whom I shall give
a sop when I have dipped it." And when
he had dipped the sop, he gave it to
Judas's Scariot, the son of Simon. And
after the sop, Satan entered into him.
Then said Jesus unto him, "That thou
doest do quickly."
uh mention nothing about deny thyself
there but go ahead guest caller but
>> what he said that mean you taken over by
a a a demon a dark spirit isn't that
what he said
>> uh he yes he gives Matthew 16 verse 24
for that one saying does that imply the
dark forces can assess your bodies and
use us for their own purposes.
>> No, he can't. Now, there's another Now,
he said that's right there. Use this
same Judas. Uh the Lord uh uh it said
that uh uh we just got through reading.
What did Judas, what did it say again?
>> It said it said verse uh 26 says, "Jesus
answered, he it is to whom I shall give
a sop when I have dipped it." And when
he had dipped the sop, he gave it to
Judas a Scariot the son of Simon. And
after the sop Satan entered into him,
then said Jesus unto him that thou doest
do quickly.
>> Now there's another tell you that that
the Lord that Satan put it on Jesus
mind.
Somebody find that it's the same thing.
>> I think you're looking for then enter
Satan into Judas.
>> What now? Then enter Satan into Judas.
>> No, let him know that Satan uh put it in
Judah's mind.
>> Oh, okay.
>> Yeah, that's John uh it's two places.
John 13 and two.
>> Yeah.
>> Okay.
>> It says, "And supper ended, the devil
having now put into the heart of Judas's
Scariot, Simon's son, to betray him."
Now, he didn't go inside of Judas. He
said he put it in Judah's mind. In other
words, he influencing him.
>> Okay.
>> Yeah.
>> Just like uh uh uh uh
Satan influenced Eve
to eat of the tree of the knowledge and
good and evil. He didn't take her over.
The book said he deceived her.
That's all I have to say.
>> Yeah. And uh I think they was that
scripture when they was talking about
deny thyself. Let's go there Luke 9.
>> Luke 93
>> and read that 23 and uh 24.
>> Okay. Luke 9 23 and 24 says,
>> this is Jesus talking here, so keep this
in mind. Go ahead. And he said to them
all, "If any man will come after me, let
him deny himself and take up his cross
daily and follow me. For whosoever will
save his life shall lose it. But
whosoever will lose his life for my
sake, the same shall save it." Mhm.
>> So when he's talking about denying
himself, you got to pick up all the ways
of Jesus and make him first in your life
and you have to follow him. So you have
to deny you and put him first in your
life. Anybody else?
>> Well, Paul said in Romans the 7th
chapter said it here. That's uh uh
>> Romans 7.
>> Uhhuh. And we going uh uh we going to
read verse 24 and 25.
>> Oh wretched man.
>> Start at verse 23.
>> Okay. Romans 7 and verse 23-2
says, "But I see another law in my
members, warning against the law of my
mind, and bringing me into captivity to
the law of sin which is in my members."
>> Oh, wretched
What he mean in his members is mean that
uh you want to uh uh break God's
commandment. You want to steal somebody
money. You want to sleep with somebody's
wife
and you want to uh uh do things that you
enjoy, but the law says thou shalt not.
So that's why he said, you know, there's
a law in your memor because you want to
do a lot of things that's contrary to
God's commandment. Go ahead.
>> Oh wretched man that I am, who shall
deliver me from the body of this death.
I thank God through Jesus Christ our
Lord. So then with the mind I myself
serve the law of God, but with the flesh
the law of sin.
So now all he's saying is with the flesh
all of a sudden you want to go and lay
with a woman outside of your wife
or get a chance to steal a great big
piece of money. That is what you want to
do. But you have to deny yourself and
don't steal
>> and don't commit adultery. That's all
it's saying.
>> That's right. Yeah. So get up, get up
every day and fight that good fight of
faith
that you may win eternal life. All
right, Sister Deborah, time check.
>> Yes, the time is 9:07.
>> We have ran out of time and we want to
thank everybody from all around the
world who sent in those questions. We
thank you for joining us this evening.
If you submitted a question and we
didn't get to it, don't resubmit it.
Sister Deborah, take it. put it in
rotation and we will answer that
question next week. So until we all come
together again, be safe, be careful, and
stay prayed up as brother James closes
us out.
Our Father, which art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name. Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done in earth as it is in
heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread. And
forgive us our debts as we forgive our
debtors. And lead us not into
temptation, but deliver us from evil.
For thine is the kingdom and the power
and the glory forever. In Jesus name we
pray. Amen.